{
    "subject": "resource/Leonardo_Benvenuti",
    "predicate": "ontology/birthYear",
    "object": "1923",
    "human_readable": "Leonardo Benvenuti was born in 1923.",
    "questions": [
        {
            "score": 0.9087611436843872,
            "question": "When was Leonardo Benvenuti born?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.900751531124115,
            "question": "In what century was Leonardo Benvenuti born?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.7271082401275635,
            "question": "What year is associated with Leonardo Benvenuti's birth?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.6141512989997864,
            "question": "Is Leonardo Benvenuti older or younger than someone born in 1950?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.5549091100692749,
            "question": "What major advancements or discoveries likely happened around the time of Leonardo Benvenuti's birth?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.450129896402359,
            "question": "How old would Leonardo Benvenuti be today?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.438003271818161,
            "question": "Can you think of any famous people who were also born in 1923?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.42569923400878906,
            "question": "What significant historical events may have occurred during Leonardo Benvenuti's lifetime?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.30414560437202454,
            "question": "What are some potential career paths or interests that someone born in 1923 might have pursued?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.28503626585006714,
            "question": "If Leonardo Benvenuti lived through World War II, what impact might it have had on his life?"
        }
    ],
    "google_pages": [
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Leonardo Benvenuti was born in 1923.",
            "html": "dbpedia_5437_0.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=What are some potential career paths or interests that someone born in 1923 might have pursued?",
            "html": "dbpedia_5437_1.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=What significant historical events may have occurred during Leonardo Benvenuti's lifetime?",
            "html": "dbpedia_5437_2.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Can you think of any famous people who were also born in 1923?",
            "html": "dbpedia_5437_3.html"
        }
    ],
    "selected_docs": [
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_5437_1.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_5437_13.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_5437_2.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_5437_28.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_5437_35.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_5437_37.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_5437_45.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_5437_51.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_5437_66.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_5437_67.txt"
        }
    ],
    "final_question": "Is true?",
    "responses": {
        "gemma2": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{'output': 'yes'}\n``` \n"
        },
        "llama3.1": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{\n  \"output\": \"yes\"\n}\n```\n\nAll the documents mention that Leonardo Benvenuti was born in 1923, with some documents specifying the exact date as September 8, 1923. Therefore, the triple is supported by the information in the documents."
        },
        "qwen2.5": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{\n  \"output\": \"yes\"\n}\n```\n\nThe documents state that Leonardo Benvenuti was born on September 8, 1923, which supports the statement that he was born in 1923."
        },
        "mistral": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": " {\"output\": \"yes\"}"
        }
    },
    "need_tiebreaker": false,
    "tiebreakers_responses": {
        "qwen2.5:14b": {},
        "llama3.1:70b": {}
    },
    "final_decision": 1,
    "actual_decision": 1,
    "analysis": {
        "stratum": "Popular",
        "topic": "-"
    },
    "errors": {}
}